<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Matthäus J. Mrozek</title>
    <link>https://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Matthäus J. Mrozek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 06:04:20 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Recap Week 41 (2023)</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/recapweek412023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 06:04:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/recapweek412023/</guid>
      <description>Survey
Several times during the week I write down important events from my life, interesting facts, thoughts and opinions on various topics and then present a selection of them in the form of a single post, like this one that I’m currently reading. The other option would be to post several times during the week and thus create shorter, more compact and more topic-specific posts. I would be interested to know which option you like better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recap Week 40 (2023)</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/recapweek402023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 06:04:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/recapweek402023/</guid>
      <description>General on Weekly Reviews, Job Offer, Purpose of Reels, Artist Website
How should I start this weekly review? Like in school with an introduction, main body, and conclusion? I’m constantly aware that this text, the blog post, and consequently the reel, are public. But that’s the point. I want to provide insights into my work, let you all participate in my life, and open myself to constructive criticism. I’ll get used to this scrutiny eventually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Postscript on: Recap Week 38 (2023)</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/recapweek38postscript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 06:20:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/recapweek38postscript/</guid>
      <description>It was my first Reel with voiceover, and for the first time, I offered a relatively deep insight into my life in this format. Therefore, I was especially eager to see your reactions and the number of views, which is why I watched it myself multiple times. This felt like a change in perspective. As soon as the Reel was online, I viewed it differently and, above all, more closely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recap Week 38 (2023)</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/recapweek382023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 06:02:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/recapweek382023/</guid>
      <description>It was 2019, and I abandoned my original plan. Instead of becoming a lecturer in language philosophy, I pivoted. Driven by a passion for technology and entrepreneurial ambition, I furthered my education in product development, systems engineering, WordPress, and so on.
Fast forward to the summer of 2021. I mustered the courage, quit my student job at a transshipment base, became a freelancer, and began designing websites and offering IT support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing JP’s ’12 Rules for Life’ – 3 (Preface, Paragraph 1)</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/jp3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 16:27:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/jp3/</guid>
      <description>During my time at university, I was constantly overwhelmed. Family, financial, and health issues, a physically demanding part-time job in a warehouse, exam stress at university, and a slew of other tasks and duties weighed on me so much that I lost my zest for life and often didn’t even want to get out of bed in the morning. In search of help in simplifying my life, Google quickly pointed me to an article from a psychology magazine that answered the question: “Getting through life with just two rules: Is it possible?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing JP’s ’12 Rules for Life’ – 2 (Introduction: Reasons for my JP Posts)</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/jp2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 16:27:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/jp2/</guid>
      <description>Why should one read my JP series? I anticipate this very probable and reasonable question from my intrigued website visitors. I hereby present some features, ideas, characteristics, etc., and thus explain my approach to analyzing the book by describing it.
A practical book, like a guide to successful Bonsai care, focuses on a small, particularly delicate, beautiful, yet relatively simple subject. Accordingly, a directive like “Trim the leaves regularly with a specialized scissors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing JP’s ’12 Rules for Life’ – 1 (Introduction: My Reasons for Reading)</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/jp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 16:27:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/jp1/</guid>
      <description>My initial encounter with JP might be considered unusual. At some point, YouTube, for reasons unknown, directed my attention to a hearing in the Canadian Senate regarding Bill C-16. It wasn’t the content of the hearing that struck me but rather how JP presented himself. Surrounded by politicians, experts, lawyers, etc., he defended himself, counter-attacked, argued, and provided information. To me, it seemed as if a group of exceptionally intelligent individuals pooled their intellectual might and yet faltered before a single individual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fracture, Jack, the Tank, Mother</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/fracture/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 06:02:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/fracture/</guid>
      <description>A Fracture
My little sister looks at me with a peculiar expression, holds two connected track pieces, and threatens to break them if I don’t pick her up. I suffer a hernia, but I still hold her. The Christ child focuses only on me. I don’t feel any pain. My mother chides, “Don’t kick your socks onto the wardrobe again!” I simply lose interest in playing with the toy train. Rather, I’m still enamored by the toy, but fear currently dominates my emotions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reaction to my YouTube playlist on the topic “Meta-competencies”: Part 1 (Preamble, Introduction, List)</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/reaction1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 06:01:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/reaction1/</guid>
      <description>It’s morning. I’m in my small, cozy attic apartment. The first coffee of the day has been made and sits next to me in a large mug labeled “Crisis Manager.” I’ll drink it shortly, as I’ve just had a large amount of vegetable juice and am now quite full – too full, even for a single sip of coffee.
Today, I must draft a rough version of my text on meta-skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal or professional website?</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 16:19:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/hub/</guid>
      <description>This website is a hub, but not in the way a switch star-connects network nodes; it’s more like a person in an immutable center, seemingly chaotically amalgamating various areas of life, or fields, within itself.
From the menu, it’s clear where everything is located, allowing a friend to effortlessly find an essay, and a potential client to swiftly access my portfolio, which predominantly contains IT projects.
For many years, I was a student, then an employee.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
