<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>recap on Matthäus J. Mrozek</title>
    <link>https://example.org/tags/recap/</link>
    <description>Recent content in recap on Matthäus J. Mrozek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 06:04:20 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.org/tags/recap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Recap Week 41 (2023)</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/recapweek412023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 06:04:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/recapweek412023/</guid>
      <description>Survey
Several times during the week I write down important events from my life, interesting facts, thoughts and opinions on various topics and then present a selection of them in the form of a single post, like this one that I’m currently reading. The other option would be to post several times during the week and thus create shorter, more compact and more topic-specific posts. I would be interested to know which option you like better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recap Week 40 (2023)</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/recapweek402023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 06:04:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/recapweek402023/</guid>
      <description>General on Weekly Reviews, Job Offer, Purpose of Reels, Artist Website
How should I start this weekly review? Like in school with an introduction, main body, and conclusion? I’m constantly aware that this text, the blog post, and consequently the reel, are public. But that’s the point. I want to provide insights into my work, let you all participate in my life, and open myself to constructive criticism. I’ll get used to this scrutiny eventually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Postscript on: Recap Week 38 (2023)</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/recapweek38postscript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 06:20:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/recapweek38postscript/</guid>
      <description>It was my first Reel with voiceover, and for the first time, I offered a relatively deep insight into my life in this format. Therefore, I was especially eager to see your reactions and the number of views, which is why I watched it myself multiple times. This felt like a change in perspective. As soon as the Reel was online, I viewed it differently and, above all, more closely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recap Week 38 (2023)</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/recapweek382023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 06:02:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/recapweek382023/</guid>
      <description>It was 2019, and I abandoned my original plan. Instead of becoming a lecturer in language philosophy, I pivoted. Driven by a passion for technology and entrepreneurial ambition, I furthered my education in product development, systems engineering, WordPress, and so on.
Fast forward to the summer of 2021. I mustered the courage, quit my student job at a transshipment base, became a freelancer, and began designing websites and offering IT support.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
